[
    {
        "front": "<b>Q1. When developing a backlink strategy, what approach would be most beneficial?</b>\n- Guest post the article to as many sites as possible\n- Create an infographics and share it with relevant bloggers\n- Create diverse and unnatural links\n- Distribute links in comment sections of websites",
        "back": "Guest post the article to as many sites as possible"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q2. What is a key reason the URL `domain.com/apparel/jackets` is preferable to the URL `domain.com/p=141`?</b>\n- It is longer\n- It is not preferable\n- It uses structured markup\n- It is readable to a human",
        "back": "It is readable to a human"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q3. Which HTTP response status code would indicate a page has been moved permanently?</b>\n- 410\n- 302\n- 200\n- 301",
        "back": "301"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q4. You notice a website is serving HTML to a Search Engine than to a human user. What is this an example of?</b>\n- Spam injection\n- Cloaking\n- Sneaky Redirect\n- Splicing",
        "back": "Cloaking"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q5. What would significantly improve Google&#39;s ability to a non-YouTube video in its Search Results?</b>\n- Provide a 150 x 80 pixel thumbnail image\n- Add Schema.org VideoObject\n- Convert .mp4 videos to .mov\n- Embed video objects with JavaScript conditionals",
        "back": "Add Schema.org VideoObject"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q6. Google primarily determines indexing and ranking by crawling which version of a page?</b>\n- Responsive version\n- Submitted version\n- Mobile version\n- Desktop version",
        "back": "Responsive version"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q7. You want to identify which US state has the most search interest for a particular keyword. What tool would help you determine this?</b>\n- Google Analytics\n- Google Keyword Planner\n- Google Search Console\n- Google Trends",
        "back": "Google Trends"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q8. You want to block crawlers from accessing your entire website. What robots.txt entry would you use?</b>\n- :\n```markdown\n    User-agent: Allbots\n    Disallow: \\*\n```\n- :\n```markdown\n    User-agent: /\n    Disallow: \\*\n```\n- :\n```markdown\n    User-agent: /\n    Disallow:\n```\n- :\n```markdown\n    User-agent: \\*\n    Disallow: /\n```",
        "back": ":\n```markdown\n    User-agent: \\*\n    Disallow: /\n```"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q9. Which result is most likely if you use an interstitial pop-up that requires a user to take action before you load the content of the page?</b>\n- Both the pop-up and the content of the page will be indexed\n- The pop-up will be indexed instead of the desired body content\n- An interstitial pop-up is treated the same as a soft 404\n- The pop-up will be ignored, and the content of the page will be indexed correctly",
        "back": "The pop-up will be indexed instead of the desired body content"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q10. You notice a particular product in an e-commerce storefront is no longer indexed, despite no technical issues. What is a likely reason for this?</b>\n- No title or meta description tags were provided\n- The Keywords is too competitive\n- Robots.txt is configured to allow access\n- The product is out of stock",
        "back": "No title or meta description tags were provided"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q11. All byline dates for articles are suddenly no longer visible on a `website&#39;s` listing within Google Search. Assuming no changes have been made to the site programming or content, what is the most likely cause?</b>\n- The site has been delisted from Google Search\n- A Google News sitemap was not provided within 30 days of setting up a publisher center account\n- The site kept updating the dates to make the content appear fres, without changing\n- The articles have aged more than 365 days without any significant updates to the content or the site",
        "back": "The site kept updating the dates to make the content appear fres, without changing"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q12. Which approach is not advisable to Geo-targeting your website?</b>\n- Using a gTLD with subdomain\n- using URL parameters\n- Using a ccTLD\n- Using a gTLD with a subdirectory",
        "back": "using URL parameters"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q13. You have been asked to help a big e-commerce brand optimize their website for search engines. They currently have thousands of products listed on their website. What is your most appropriate first step?</b>\n- Recommend that they add more products\n- Work on compressing image files\n- 302 redirect all product pages to URL that contains target keywords\n- Register the business with a Google My Business account.",
        "back": "Work on compressing image files"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q14. What Does The Term &quot;Sandbox&quot; Mean In SEO?</b>\n- The Box With Paid Ads That Appear When You Perform A Search.\n- This Is Where Sites Are Kept Till They Get Mature Enough To Be Included In The Top Rankings For A Particular Keyword\n- A Special Category Of Sites That Are Listed In Kid-safe Searches\n- The First 10 Search Results For A Particular Keyword.",
        "back": "This Is Where Sites Are Kept Till They Get Mature Enough To Be Included In The Top Rankings For A Particular Keyword"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q15. What Is Anchor Text?</b>\n- It Is The Main Body Of Text On A Particular Web Page\n- It Is The Text Within The Left Or Top Panel Of A Web Page\n- It Is The Visible Text That Is Hyper Linked To Another Page\n- It Is The Most Prominent Text On The Page That The Search Engines Use To Assign A Title To The Page",
        "back": "It Is The Visible Text That Is Hyper Linked To Another Page"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q16. Which Google search query should be used to return only PDF documents that reference Microsoft?</b>\n- Microsoft + .pdf\n- \"Microsoft\" + \"pdf\"\n- Microsoft AND \"pdf\"\n- Microsoft filetype:pdf",
        "back": "Microsoft filetype:pdf"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q17. Which link is not crawlable?</b>\n- `<a href=\"http://domain.com\">`\n- `<a onclick=\"newwin('domain.com')\">`\n- `<a href=\"http://domain.com\" class=\"blue\">`\n- `<a href=\"../category-2/page\">`",
        "back": "`<a onclick=\"newwin('domain.com')\">`"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q18. Which choice represents the best header structure?</b>\n- :\n```markdown\n    H1: How to Bak Bagels\n    H2: Ingredients\n    H3: Dry Ingredients\n    H4: Wet Ingredients\n    H2: Instructions\n    H6: Reviews\n```\n- :\n```markdown\n    H1: How to Bak Bagels\n    H1: Ingredients\n    H1: Dry Ingredients\n    H1: Wet Ingredients\n    H1: Instructions\n    H2: Reviews\n```\n- :\n```markdown\n    H1: How to Bak Bagels\n    H2: Ingredients\n    H3: Dry Ingredients\n    H3: Wet Ingredients\n    H2: Instructions\n    H2: Reviews\n```\n- :\n```markdown\n    H1: How to Bak Bagels\n    H2: Ingredients\n    H4: Dry Ingredients\n    H5: Wet Ingredients\n    H6: Instructions\n    H1: Reviews\n```",
        "back": ":\n```markdown\n    H1: How to Bak Bagels\n    H2: Ingredients\n    H3: Dry Ingredients\n    H4: Wet Ingredients\n    H2: Instructions\n    H6: Reviews\n```"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q19. All byline dates articles are suddenly no longer visible on a website's listing within Google Search. Assuming no changes have been made to the site programming or content, what is the most likely cause?</b>\n- The site has been delisted from Google Search\n- The site kept updating the date to make the content appear fresh, without changing the content.\n- The articles have aged more than 365 days without any significant updates to the content or the site.\n- A Google New sitemap was not provided within 30 days of setting up a Publisher Center account",
        "back": "The site kept updating the date to make the content appear fresh, without changing the content."
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q20. What is an example of a Google search result that can be found in position zero?</b>\n- Google Ads result\n- featured snippet\n- related searches\n- autocomplete",
        "back": "featured snippet"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q21. When creating accessible video content, what should you consider including?</b>\n- transcript\n- thumbnail\n- Flash Player\n- event tracking",
        "back": "transcript"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q22. You are optimizing a website that sells supplies for banking donuts. Which approach is most appropriate to drive more organic traffic?</b>\n- Buy donutbakingsupplies.com and 301 redirect to your website\n- Add the keyword \"donut supplies\" to every page.\n- Create a new blog with high-quality donut recipes\n- Join a link farm to rapidly build inbounnd links.",
        "back": "Create a new blog with high-quality donut recipes"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q23. Why is it important to be mindful of outbound follow links?</b>\n- There is a limit to how many links you can create.\n- all of these answers\n- Any follow links reduce your PageRank by 1.\n- Your site's reputation is tied to the sites you link to.",
        "back": "Your site's reputation is tied to the sites you link to."
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q24. Which statement is true about JSON-LD?</b>\n- It has no relation to JSON.\n- It is the only structured data format available.\n- It is considered the most complicated approach to adding structured data.\n- It is Google's preferred structured data format.",
        "back": "It is Google's preferred structured data format."
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q25. What is a key reason why duplicate content might cause an issue with ranking?</b>\n- It creates an inability to use canonical URLs, which dramatically reduces crawl effectiveness,\n- It requires using a 302 redirect, which dilutes PageRank.\n- It triggers an immediate manual action penalty, which delists an entire domain until the duplicate content is removed.\n- It makes it difficult for a search engine to determine the original and authoritative content source.",
        "back": "It makes it difficult for a search engine to determine the original and authoritative content source."
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q26. What attribute would you use to describe the content of an image?</b>\n- tabindex\n- longdesc\n- src\n- alt",
        "back": "alt"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q27. You are researching keywords for a client and creating list for an optimization plan. Which is _not_ a recommended method of creating keyword lists?</b>\n- synonyms and related words\n- queries about benefits, features, problems\n- how-to and question-based queries\n- focusing on only high-volume, high-popularity words",
        "back": "focusing on only high-volume, high-popularity words"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q28. You want to get a rough idea of how many searches per month a particular search term gets. Which tool do you use?</b>\n- Google Keyword Planner\n- Google Tag Manager\n- Google Search Console\n- Google Suggest",
        "back": "Google Keyword Planner"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q29. Changing the title tag and/or meta description will have a measurable impact on your \\_.</b>\n- RSS\n- CTR\n- PPC\n- LSI",
        "back": "CTR"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q30. How do keywords change as people progress through the buying cycle?</b>\n- They move from simple to more complex as searchers gather more information and then refine their choices.\n- The stay simple, as searchers try to use as few words as possible.\n- The keywords do not change much at all.\n- They move from complex to simple, as searchers find answers to their questions.",
        "back": "They move from simple to more complex as searchers gather more information and then refine their choices."
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q31. Which technique is an example of black hat SEO?</b>\n- cloaking\n- keyword research\n- useful content\n- on-page optimization",
        "back": "cloaking"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q32. A local accountant wants to start attracting more business directly from Google organic search. What is the best piece of advice to give to her?</b>\n- Use the pharse \"local accountant\" as a keyword to focus her website on.\n- Focus on short-tail keywords.\n- Register her business with a Google Business Profile account.\n- Leave a link to her website in the blog comments of popular accounting websites.",
        "back": "Register her business with a Google Business Profile account."
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q33. What is the anchor text in this code sample?</b>\n`<a href=\"catalog/gloves.html\">Blue Gloves</a>`\n- Blue Gloves\n- href\n- catalog/\n- gloves.html",
        "back": "Blue Gloves"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q34. **\\_** analysis allows you to review requests made to your web server to identify insights such as how ofter a crawler arrives, what pages have 404 errors, and most crawled pages</b>\n- Log file\n- HTTP/2\n- Cron job\n- Resource packet",
        "back": "Log file"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q35. Which page title references content that is evergreen</b>\n- Mega List of Teams Going to the Olympics\n- Complete Coverage of Microsoft's Latest Announcement\n- The Future of SEO in 2020\n- How to Reheat Pizza",
        "back": "How to Reheat Pizza"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q36. You load a page and start reading an article, and suddenly the content on the page moves. What metric is used to quantify this impact on user experience?</b>\n- First Meaningful Paint (FMP)\n- Recalculated Style Timing (RST)\n- Latent Loading Signal (LLS)\n- Cumulative Layout Shift (CLS)",
        "back": "Cumulative Layout Shift (CLS)"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q37. What is this code is an example of?</b>\n```<script type=\"application/ld+json\">\n{\n   \"@context\": \"https://schema.org\",\n   \"@type\": \"Organization\",\n   \"url\": \"http://www.domain.com\",\n   \"name\": \"Bradley Corp.\",\n   \"contactPoint\": {\n      \"@type\": \"ContactPoint\",\n      \"telephone\": \"+1-555-555-5555\",\n      \"contactType\": \"Customer service\"\n    }\n}\n</script>\n```\n- meta tag\n- HTTP response\n- XML sitemap\n- structured data",
        "back": "structured data"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q38. Which search query would be most difficult to determine search intent?</b>\n- XBox live coupon\n- Microsoft Office 365\n- LinkedIn login\n- LAX airport directions",
        "back": "Microsoft Office 365"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q39. When you conduct a search, what are the bolded words within the search listing description?</b>\n- suggested search terms\n- related search queries\n- keywords that match the search query\n- words with a `<b>` tag assigned in their meta description",
        "back": "keywords that match the search query"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q40. Which acronym is used to describe the page a user sees after submitting a search?</b>\n- SERP (Search Engine Results Page)\n- INDX\n- PARS\n- SEM",
        "back": "SERP (Search Engine Results Page)"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q41. Which statement is true regarding the use of social signals, such as LinkedIn shares, by Google in its ranking algorithm?</b>\n- Google does not use social signals to determine rank\n- Social signals are identical to backlinks\n- Social signals are used to determine topic authority\n- Social signals provide a benefit only if they have structured data markup",
        "back": "Social signals are used to determine topic authority"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q42. A user clicks an internal link resulting in this redirect chain: `http://domain.com -> https://domain.com -> https://domain.com/`. In this example, what is being consumed unnecessarily?</b>\n- redirect allotment\n- crawl budget\n- velocity scale\n- domain authority",
        "back": "redirect allotment"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q43. You are planning for the development of an e-commerce website. Which approach will be more beneficial for rankings?</b>\n- Optimize the front page of your website to drive traffic from all category search terms.\n- Optimize product category pages to drive traffic from individual category search terms.\n- Optimize all pages on the site for all category search terms.\n- Optimize product pages to drive traffic from individual category search terms.",
        "back": "Optimize all pages on the site for all category search terms."
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q44. What is the relationship of click depth to PageRank?</b>\n- The deeper the click depth, the lower the PageRank\n- PageRank and click depth have no relation\n- The deeper the click depth, the higher the PageRank\n- Click depth and PageRank are equal",
        "back": "The deeper the click depth, the lower the PageRank"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q45. What is a popular technique for writing content with the goal of having it appear in a features snippet?</b>\n- Write the question in a headline tag, and then answer it below in a format that matches the snippet type.\n- Use the features snippet schema and apply an object that matches the correct snippet type.\n- Google manually generates featured snippets, so there is no special technique.\n- Submit the content through Google Search Console, and tag it with the correct snippet type.",
        "back": "Write the question in a headline tag, and then answer it below in a format that matches the snippet type."
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q46. What is a common best practice for handling search result pages on a blog's built-in site search?</b>\n- Set site research results to no-index.\n- Do not use site search.\n- Set site search to 404.\n- Add a canonical from the search result page to the home page.",
        "back": "Set site research results to no-index."
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q47. What might help a search engine understand the difference between an article on a dog bark versus tree bark?</b>\n- tertiary analysis\n- ranked choice trees\n- semantic analysis\n- knowledge graphs",
        "back": "semantic analysis"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q48. A webpage has this tag: `<title>Brad's Bagels: How to Bake a Bagel</title>`. However, the Google search result for this page displays this title: \\_Brad's Bagels: Baking Bagels in the Oven\\_. What is a likely explanation?</b>\n- The title tag was placed within the <HEAD> section of the webpage, but not before the meta content tags, so Google cannot identify the actual title.\n- The page is using structured data to define an alternative title object, which allows the search engine to pick a preferable version.\n- A breadcrumb navigation is in use, which overrides the title tag supplied in the HTML.\n- Google generated a new title using text on the page that more closely matched the search query.",
        "back": "The page is using structured data to define an alternative title object, which allows the search engine to pick a preferable version."
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q49. What alt attribute should be assigned to an image of a decorative line being used to separate content</b>\n- alt=\"\"\n- alt=\"Thin black line being used to seperate two blocks of content\"\n- alt=\"dec\"\n- alt=\"thin-line\"",
        "back": "alt=\"Thin black line being used to seperate two blocks of content\""
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q50. Your site serves identical content when you visit domain.com/page or domain.com/page?ref=123. What should you implement?</b>\n- parameter stripping\n- URL cloaking\n- a 302 redirect\n- a rel=canonical link",
        "back": "a rel=canonical link"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q51. What data vocabulary is most commonly used when marking up content on a page?</b>\n- vocabulary.org\n- RDFa.org\n- schema.org\n- data-vocabulary.org",
        "back": "schema.org"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q52. According to Google, what type of content includes topics such as news, legal issues, financial advice, and medical information?</b>\n- RSS\n- KYC\n- YMYL\n- BDB",
        "back": "YMYL\n\n**Explanation:** `Google describes YMYL (Your Money or Your Life) sites/pages as ones that could potentially impact a person\u2019s happiness, health, financial stability, or safety.`"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q53. When would it be necessary to 301 redirect every page on a site?</b>\n- when parameters are used in URLs\n- when migrating from HTTP to HTTPS\n- when launching a new redesign\n- when creating a new subdomain",
        "back": "when migrating from HTTP to HTTPS\n\n**Explanation:** From article: [301 Redirects for SEO](https://ahrefs.com/blog/301-redirects/) (2020)"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q54. What would contribute to a low bounce rate?</b>\n- Content does not match search intent.\n- Page returns 404 error.\n- Content reflects search intent.\n- URL uses parameters.",
        "back": "Content reflects search intent."
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q55. What should be as consistent as possible across the web when developing a local SEO strategy?</b>\n- backlinks\n- NAP\n- LRP\n- inbound links\n1. [reference](https://support.google.com/business/answer/7091)\n2. [reference #2](https://www.smartinsights.com/search-engine-optimisation-seo/how-to-adjust-your-nap-profile-for-local-seo/)",
        "back": "NAP"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q56. A user enters a search \\_ to retrieve results from a search engine?</b>\n- query\n- parser\n- bar\n- link",
        "back": "query"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q57. The search query \"How to make donuts without yeast\" is an example of what?</b>\n- fresh keyword\n- operative keyword\n- short-tail keyword\n- long-tail keyword",
        "back": "long-tail keyword"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q58. What tool enables companies to display extra information within the natural search results without the need of any structured data?</b>\n- Google Input Tools\n- structured data testing tool\n- Google Tag Manager\n- Google My Business",
        "back": "Google My Business"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q59. Your client is ready to start a blog. but has read that they should put the blog on a subdomain instead of subdirectory in order to create more external links to their website. How would you advise your client about this strategy?</b>\n- Not only should the blog be on a subdomain, but each of the major navigation areas should be on separate subdomains in order to increase the number and value of the links into the primary domain.\n- It is best to have the blog on a subdirectory and build links to primary domain.\n- It is an advisable choice as it will enable interlinking between the domains and increase the number of links.\n- The blog should be on a separate URL to avouud building too many links between the same domain or IP.",
        "back": "It is best to have the blog on a subdirectory and build links to primary domain."
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q60. Blog author pages, each with only one sentence about the author, are at risk of being flagged as **\\_** content.</b>\n- non-indexable\n- irrelevant\n- biased\n- thin",
        "back": "thin"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q61. What is a common benefit to long-tail keywords?</b>\n- They are less competitive, and may have higher conversion rates.\n- Long-tail keywords are no longer relevant in today's SEO landscape.\n- They are less grandular, so you capture broader searches.\n- They are more competitive, but drive significantly more traffic.",
        "back": "They are less competitive, and may have higher conversion rates."
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q62. You have been asked to help a big e-commerce brand optimize their website for search engines. They currently have thousands of products listed on their website. What is your most appropriate first step?</b>\n- Set campaign goals.\n- Conduct a technical audit.\n- Conduct a backlink audit.\n- Determine keyword strategy.",
        "back": "Conduct a technical audit."
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q63. You are optimizing a large e-commerce website. Which strategy will likely yield the most organic traffic?</b>\n- Launch a Smart Shopping Campaign in Google Ads.\n- Optimize the home page of your website.\n- Optimize each product page with a unique product-specific keyword.\n- Optimize your product category pages.",
        "back": "Optimize each product page with a unique product-specific keyword."
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q64. Google's Search Quality Evaluator Guidelines describe that experts should write content, especially YMYL content. This is one of the principles seen in the commonly used acronym\\_\\_</b>\n- A.C.E\n- L-E-A-F\n- T.R.U.S.T.E.D\n- E-A-T",
        "back": "E-A-T\n\n[Reference](https://moz.com/blog/google-e-a-t)"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q65. Why might using a subdirectory in place of a subdomain be beneficial?</b>\n- Using a subdirectory is never preferable to using a subdomain.\n- The subdirectory will allow for keyword dilution.\n- The subdirectory will benefit from the backlinks the domain has acquired.\n- The subdirectory is better for the end user experience.",
        "back": ""
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q66. What is the best way to provide a search engine with crawl instructions?</b>\n- Use the <crawl> tag.\n- Use the search engine's Remove URL tool.\n- Use a robots.txt file.\n- Use structured data",
        "back": "Use a robots.txt file."
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q67. You are optimizing a site that receives a lot of user-submitted comments, many of which contain a promotional links. According to SEO best practices, how should you treat the comments?</b>\n- Be sure links are using keywork-rich anchor tags\n- Disallow each link submitted\n- Set links in comments to be Nofollow\n- Bold important keywords in comments",
        "back": "Set links in comments to be Nofollow"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q68. What is not a primary component of a SERP snippet?</b>\n- Description\n- Title\n- Cache\n- URL",
        "back": "Cache"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q69. A landing page with no internal or external links is an example of what?</b>\n- Dynamic hierarchy\n- Doorway content\n- Orphaned content\n- Flat Hierarchy",
        "back": "Orphaned content"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q70. Informational, navigational, commercial, transactional are four categories of what?</b>\n- keyword search intent\n- crawling\n- indexing\n- HTTP responses",
        "back": "keyword search intent"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q71. How many H1 tags are typically found on a single page?</b>\n- up to five\n- one\n- as many as necessary\n- two",
        "back": "one"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q72. What is a meta description used for?</b>\n- to summarize the content of a webpage\n- to bundle meta tags\n- to describe images\n- to assign schema markup",
        "back": "to summarize the content of a webpage"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q73. Which tool would be best to use to research how many searches per month a term gets?</b>\n- Google Search Console\n- Google Suggest\n- Google Keyword Planner\n- Google Tag Manager",
        "back": "Google Keyword Planner"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q74. What is an example of a top-level domain (TLD)?</b>\n- .net\n- domain.ai\n- www\n- 301",
        "back": ".net\n\n[Reference](https://www.techopedia.com/definition/1348/top-level-domain-tld)"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q75. What does the 301 server response code signify?</b>\n- Not Modified\n- Moved Permanently\n- Payment is required\n- Syntax error in the request\n`Explanation: The HyperText Transfer Protocol (HTTP) 301 Moved Permanently redirect status response code indicates that the requested resource has been definitively moved to the URL given by the Location headers. A browser redirects to the new URL and search engines update their links to the resource.`",
        "back": "Moved Permanently"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q75. What tag should you use to signal the main topic heading of a page?</b>\n- `<h1>`\n- `<h0>`\n- `<strong>`\n- `<em>`",
        "back": "`<h1>`\n\n[Reference](https://blog.hubspot.com/marketing/header-tags)"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q76. What term is typically used to explain the shuffling of positions in search engine results in between significant updates?</b>\n- Flux\n- Waves\n- Swaying\n- Shuffling",
        "back": "Flux"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q77. Which of the following declarations about FFA web pages are true?</b>\n- They are paid listings.\n- They are also called link farms.\n- They are significantly beneficial to search engine optimization.\n- They contain various inbound links.",
        "back": "They are also called link farms."
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q78. What is the generally approved distinction in between SEO and also SEM?</b>\n- SEO refers to organic/natural listings while sem covers pay per click, or paid search.\n- Search engine optimization focuses on organic/natural search positions, sem encompasses all facets of search marketing.\n- No difference, they're synonymous.\n- SEO has a tendency to be a west shore term, sem is much more eastern shore.",
        "back": "Search engine optimization focuses on organic/natural search positions, sem encompasses all facets of search marketing."
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q79. Which of the following link building techniques do online search engine tacitly recommend?</b>\n- Reciprocal link exchange programs.\n- Viral content creation & promotion.\n- Renting out pages from trustworthy domains and also positioning web links on them.\n- Purchasing web links from web link brokers & networks.",
        "back": "Viral content creation & promotion."
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q80. What is the full form of SEO?</b>\n- Search Engine Optimum.\n- Search Engine Optimization.\n- Search Electronic Optimization.\n- None of the above.",
        "back": "Search Engine Optimization."
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q81. Which of the following is the process of fetching all the web pages connected to a web site?</b>\n- Indexing\n- Crawling\n- Processing\n- All of the Above",
        "back": "Crawling"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q82. What does the 302 server response code signify?</b>\n- It symbolizes dispute, way too many individuals desired the exact same documents at the same time.\n- The web page has actually been permanently removed.\n- The technique you are making use of to access the file is not allowed.\n- The web page has actually temporarily moved.\n- What you requested is just also large to process.",
        "back": "The web page has actually temporarily moved."
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q83. Which of the following declarations about RSS are proper?</b>\n- It is a form of XML.\n- It stands for Realtime streamlined syndication.\n- It is an excellent way of presenting static information.\n- It is a microsoft technology.",
        "back": "It is a form of XML."
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q84. Which of the following search engines or directories supplies the major search results for AOL?</b>\n- Lycos\n- DMOZ\n- Google\n- Yahoo",
        "back": "Google"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q85. Google gives priority to themed in-bound links.</b>\n- True\n- False",
        "back": "True"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q86. Which of the following methods can help you get around the Google Sandbox?</b>\n- Buying an old Website as well as getting it ranked.\n- Buying a Google Adwords PPC campaign.\n- Placing the website on a sub domain of a ranked site and afterwards 301 re-directing the site after it has actually been indexed.\n- Getting a DMOZ listing.",
        "back": "Buying an old Website as well as getting it ranked."
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q87. Google looks down upon paid links for enhancing page ranking. If a web site sells web links, what action/s does Google suggest to avoid being penalized?</b>\n- The text of the paid links should state words \"paid text link\" for Google to recognize it as a paid web link.\n- Only Paid text web links to non profit websites should be accepted.\n- Paid links need to be divulged via the \"rel= nofollow\" attribute in the hyperlink.\n- Paid links ought to be disclosed through the \"index= nofollow\" attribute in the hyperlink.",
        "back": "Paid links need to be divulged via the \"rel= nofollow\" attribute in the hyperlink."
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q88. What will take place if you type the word 'Certification-Python' in the Google search box?</b>\n- Google will certainly locate the web pages about \"certification\" and additionally consisting of the word \"python\".\n- Google will certainly locate ALL the web pages having the word \"Certification\" and \"Python\".\n- Google will locate ALL the web pages in which the words \"Certification\" and \"Python\" appear together.\n- Google will find the web pages about Certification that do not consist of the word Python.",
        "back": "Google will locate ALL the web pages in which the words \"Certification\" and \"Python\" appear together."
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q89. What is keyword density?</b>\n- The number of times the keyword is utilized/ (separated by) the total word count on page-- (minus) the complete words in HTML on the page.\n- The variety of times the keyword is used x (multiply by) the total word count on web page.\n- The number of times the keyword is utilized in the page description.\n- The number of times the search phrase is used in the web page title.\n- The number of times the keyword is used/ the total word count on the web page.",
        "back": "The number of times the keyword is used/ the total word count on the web page."
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q90. Which of the following statement about FFA web pages hold true?</b>\n- They are significantly beneficial to SEO.\n- They are additionally called Link Farms.\n- They are Paid Listings.\n- They contain various incoming links.",
        "back": "They are additionally called Link Farms."
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q91. What elements of a hyperlink are not important for SEO?</b>\n- The exposure of the link text.\n- The anchor text, particularly the keywords in it.\n- The area from which the web link stems.\n- The location to which the link leads.",
        "back": "The exposure of the link text."
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q92. Which of the technique is NOT an \"ideal practice\" for developing excellent quality title tags?</b>\n- Make sure the title is unique for every page\n- Include an exhaustive list of keywords\n- Limit the tag to 65 characters, including spaces\n- Write compelling copy that encourages users to \u201cclick\u201d your listing",
        "back": "Limit the tag to 65 characters, including spaces"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q93. Which HTTP web server reaction code suggests a file that no more exists? (File Not Found).</b>\n- 40A\n- 30A\n- 500\n- 404",
        "back": "404"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q94. What is Page Rank?</b>\n- The Alexa modern technology for ranking web pages.\n- The means Yahoo! actions just how popular an offered web page is based on the number as well as quality of websites that connect to it.\n- The search significance of a web page contrasted to the other web pages in the online search engine.\n- The method Google measures exactly how popular a provided page is based upon the number and also quality of sites that connect to it.",
        "back": "The method Google measures exactly how popular a provided page is based upon the number and also quality of sites that connect to it."
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q95. Your sitemap shows this entry: <lastmod>2020-09-09T19:34:00+01:00</lastmod>. What does +01:00 refer to?</b>\n- time between publishing and updating\n- time since last sitemap crawl\n- time zone designator\n- suggested content priority",
        "back": "time zone designator"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q96. What markup language is most commonly used for sitemaps?</b>\n- RSS\n- XLS\n- Javascript\n- XML",
        "back": "XML"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q97. What markup language is most commonly used for sitemaps?</b>\n- RSS\n- XLS\n- Javascript\n- XML",
        "back": "XML"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q98. You are searching for a website that was published within last week. When you type in the URL, the site does not appear in Google search results. Why might this be?</b>\n- You are searching on desktop and must wait for mobile-first indexing\n- The site is not in Google's index\n- The website needs backling to be discovered by Googlebot\n- The website does not have a high enough domain authority",
        "back": "The site is not in Google's index"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q99. In which scenario is using a 301 redirect preferred over a canonical link?</b>\n- When using faceted navigation\n- when treating uppercase versus lowercase characters in URLs\n- with an on-site search results page\n- when managing URL parameters",
        "back": "when treating uppercase versus lowercase characters in URLs"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q100. What would be most beneficial in helping a site display rich features in Google's search results?</b>\n- Google search console\n- structured data\n- Data-Vocabulary.org\n- Google Result Generator",
        "back": "structured data"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q101. Which statement is true regarding the use of social signals, such as LinkedIn shares, by Google in its ranking algorithm?</b>\n- Social signals provide a benefit only if they have structured data markup\n- Social signals are identical to backlinks\n- Google does not use social signals to determine rank\n- Social signals are used to determine topic authority",
        "back": "Social signals are used to determine topic authority\n\n[reference](https://www.gcertificationcourse.com/which-statement-is-true-regarding-the-use-of-social/)"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q102. How many outbound links should you include in each blog posting?</b>\n- at least 2\n- at least five\n- at least seven\n- as many as are relevent",
        "back": ""
    }
]